One Pace Premium
Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
A Gentle Snowfall of Remembrance
Hey! Hey, hey, hey! Usopp!
Where are you, Usopp?!
Hey!
Usopp!
Oh? He’s not up here?
Where are you, Usopp?!
Hey, he's calling for you.
O-Oh, I couldn’t possibly show my face now.
I mean it! Come out already!
If you don't come out,
I'm gonna beat the crap outta you!
We're gonna beat the crap outta you!
Hey, do you know where Usopp is, Sogeking?
I can't find him anywhere!
D-Don't worry.
He departed on a small boat, just before we did.
What?!
Why?!
But this ship actually belongs to him now.
How the hell do they not recognize that he’s Usopp?
Not here, either.
What's going on?
It’s as we thought.
There isn’t anyone anywhere on this ship.
That's strange.
I wonder who could’ve sailed this ship to us.
But we all heard the same voice calling out to us.
You did?
Yes, someone most certainly called to us.
Like I’ve been saying,
it was the Merry's voice!
What?! Really?!
Right, Merry?! Say something!
You idiot. There's no way a ship could talk.
I kinda felt that way at first,
but something like that should be impossible, right?
There’s a ship heading toward us!
Wh-What?! Who's that?!
It's the Straw Hats!
They're alive!
So you guys're okay!
A Galley-La Company ship?
This is amazing!
They rushed out in the middle of Aqua Laguna
and still made it okay! I can't believe it!
They came back from Enies Lobby!
Ahoy, Iceboss!
Stupid-burg.
Nico Robin.
What a crazy bunch.
They took on the World Government...
and really got everything back.
Merry!
Look! Their ship!
Hey, what's going on?!
What happened all of a sudden?!
All of a sudden? Isn't it only natural?
What?
The Merry was declared unfit for the seas.
But!
Merry!
Boss! This is bad! Merry is in trouble!
You gotta do something!
You guys, this is great timing!
You're all shipwrights, right?!
I'm begging you! Please do something!
She's our friend and has traveled with us for so long!
And just a bit ago she saved us!
So please, boss!
Then allow her...
to rest now.
I've already done everything I could.
What's that sound?
Is someone on Scrap Island?
Isn't this the Straw Hats' ship?
The damage from Aqua Laguna left her in bad shape.
No, she was like this before the storm.
I want to set sail.
What was that?
I want to set sail one last time!
What am I doing?
There's no hope left for this ship.
Iceburg-san!
What are you doing there?!
Another big wave is coming!
Thank you.
What?! You want to set sail?!
The storm hasn’t let up yet!
I'll go alone if I have to.
What?!
Then we can't let you go out there all by yourself!
I'm witnessing a miracle right now:
The miracle of a ship
that has long passed its limits.
In all my years as a shipwright,
I've never seen a pirate ship this remarkable.
She's lived a splendid life.
Everyone, let’s go back!
Back to the seas of adventure!
Merry!
I came to get you!
I get it.
Well then, are you guys ready?
Yeah.
Merry, the seabed is dark and lonesome,
so we’ll see you off to the very end.
Maybe it's for the best that Usopp isn't here.
There's no way... that he could bear this.
Any thoughts?
I disagree.
Everyone must someday say farewell.
This is a man's parting.
I mustn’t shed a single tear.
So he, too, is prepared.
You carried us for so long.
Thank you, Merry.
Snow!
A caravel!
We spent every day covered in mud until the sun set
Yahoo!
Now the pirate ship,
the Going Merry, is complete!
It's hard to leave behind those innocent days
Cheers to our new ship and crewmate!
I'm a dreamer because that's who I am
Look at this!
The Merry took quite a bit of damage!
When operating a ship with sails,
everyone needs to do their part!
I don't need to fit in like a piece of a jigsaw puzzle
You need to remember that!
Yes, ma'am.
Ih'm shorree.
What are you up to?
Cannon practice!
Just as someone's "Yes" could be a "No" to you,
They sure don't fly too good!
I'm telling you, let me try!
Awesome! You hit it on your first try!
You should always be free
Whoa! I really hit it on my first try!
If the puzzle is missing a piece
when the wind passes through tomorrow,
no one would blame you for that
Zoro! Hey! That's my seat!
The entrance to the Grand Line
lies just beyond that light.
To find the All Blue!
We knew we weren't wrong
To be king of the pirates!
For the dreams we had before
To become the greatest swordsman!
To draw a world map!
That helps us cross a wildly surging ocean
T-To become a brave warrior of the sea!
On to the Grand Line!
We know the pain that's in your heart,
so even if you were to get off this ship
and find yourself on the other side,
The entrance to the Grand Line is a mountain!
A mountain?
you'll surely smile in the end.
We made it!
This is the greatest sea in the world!
Keep going!
We're flying right out of it!
Don't look back!
We're keeping on straight ahead!
Let me join your crew.
I have nowhere to go
and no place to call home.
So let me stay on this ship.
Oh, I see. Then I guess we have no choice.
Okay.
We still have our dreams
Luffy!
Who's this ship's navigator?!
We're flying!
Awesome! The ship is flying!
And the memories given to us
It's Sky Island!
Today, we continue fighting the pain as we cross these rough seas
So that our promises won't become lies
And someday, to you who departed our ship to live on the other side,
we'll deliver a completed puzzle
I'm sorry;
I wanted to carry you even further.
I wanted to share adventures with you forever.
Merry!
A voice!
But I–
We’re the ones who need to apologize, Merry!
I'm not good at steering,
so I sometimes ran you into icebergs.
I also once ripped your sails!
Zoro and Sanji act stupid together,
so they broke all sorts of things!
Usopp would fix you each time,
but he wasn’t very good at it!
So we’re the ones who need to apologize!
But I've been happy.
Thank you so very much
for taking good care of me all this time.
I really have been happy...
because I had you.
Merry!